pricechopper.com 2012-05-10

# Price Chopper - Privacy

|  Security Information |  Privacy Statement | 

Price Chopper supports the consumer's right to privacy and pledges not to sell, rent or relinquish personally identifiable information to third party vendors, suppliers or marketers. 

Price Chopper does capture information from customer transactions and other information sources, including information provided to Price Chopper through your use of this web site. This information is used by Price Chopper to improve customer service, maintain proper inventories, lower costs and create special merchandising and marketing programs for shoppers who desire to participate. Only authorized Price Chopper associates have access to customer data and Price Chopper maintains strict security procedures to prevent unauthorized access to personal information. 

Price Chopper may provide non-personally identifiable compilations of information to third parties. 

If you wish to receive no promotional correspondence from Price Chopper generated from our AdvantEdge cardmember database, check the appropriate box on your AdvantEdge application form. If you have subscribed to Price Chopper's electronic newsletter and wish to unsubscribe, follow the simple instructions provided therein. If you receive other undesired electronic communication from Price Chopper, forward the correspondence to our webmaster (webmaster@pricechopper.com) and we'll work to resolve the issue promptly. 

In the operation of pharmacies, Price Chopper considers presentation of a prescription by the patient, or a request for a prescription refill, valid approval for the pharmacy to exercise its professional responsibilities, such as drug utilization review (DUR) and evaluation (DUE). 

Price Chopper pharmacies will only transfer personally identifiable information to third parties for the purpose of professional treatment, insurance reimbursement, or improved health care outcomes. 

|  Security Information |  Privacy Statement |
